// Question were taken from: https://codescracker.com/exam/sublist.php.
// All questions for the quiz are stored below.

const questions = [
    {
        question: "Swedish megastars ABBA won the 1974 Eurovision Song Contest with which song?",
        answer1: "waterloo",
        answer2: "Money Money Money",
        answer3: "Mama Mia",
        answer4: "Dancing Queen",
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is Kebnekaise",
        answer1: "Sweden's tallest mountain",
        answer2: "A Swedish delicacy",
        answer3: "Sweden's longest river",
        answer4: "A famous Swedish coffee",
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: " Which of these is the name of a pastry traditionally eaten in Sweden on the 13th of December?",
        answer1: "Semla",
        answer2: "Vaniljbulle",
        answer3: "Solskensbulle",
        answer4: "Lussekatt",
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following famous Vikings was NOT from Sweden?",
        answer1: "Ragnar lothbrok",
        answer2: "Björn Ironside",
        answer3: "Leif Eriksson",
        answer4: "Ivar the Boneless",
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the name of Sweden's national anthem?",
        answer1: "Du unga, du vackra",
        answer2: "Du gamla, du fria",
        answer3: "Du ramlar, du fisar",
        answer4: "Du fula, du fulla",
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most popular drink in Sweden?",
        answer1: "Coffee",
        answer2: "Glühwein",
        answer3: "Kiisseli",
        answer4: "Loka",
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What do Swedes do when they meet for a fika",
        answer1: "Getting drunk",
        answer2: " Handicrafts",
        answer3: "Touch each other in a sensual way",
        answer4: "Having a coffee and maybe some pastry",
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Alfred Nobel is known for this invention…",
        answer1: "Dynamite",
        answer2: "Matches",
        answer3: "Ball Bearing",
        answer4: "Hexagonal wrench",
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the national animal of Sweden?",
        answer1: "Fox",
        answer2: "Deer",
        answer3: "Moose",
        answer4: "Bear",
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What date is the national day of Sweden celebrated?",
        answer1: "6 July",
        answer2: "6 October",
        answer3: "6 May",
        answer4: "6 June",
        correct: 4
    },

];